Dad,
How
will this end?
You mean
the Deputy Brigade Commander's concerns
about the information leak,
right?
Right.
If we figure out a way
to ease his mind,
wouldn't that solve it?
Your brother gave me a call
and said Liang Hong
has found some relevant military experts.
I have some experts here too.
You should contact them later.
Then,
we'll organize the experts
to have a meeting
and look into it.
Once we come up with a practical,
feasible plan
to ease his mind,
won't this whole matter be over?
Besides,
you must apologize to the commander.
Me?
Fine.
I was indeed a bit out of line.
When I find the time,
I'll go and apologize to him.
By the way, Dad.
About this Liang Hong...
I asked around for you.
Rank of Captain, Ph.D. graduate.
Most importantly, she's single.
You asked around for me?
Who asked you to do that?
I'm locking down your future daughter-in-law.
You have no idea.
There's this kind of
chemistry between them.
A very special feeling.
Your brother and Liang Hong are in the same unit.
It's not appropriate for them to date.
Why?
Soldiers are people too.
Is there a military regulation
that two officers in the same unit
aren't allowed to date?
What do you know?
One is a Battalion Commander, one is a Staff Officer.
If a war breaks out
and they disagree,
how will the unit be commanded?
We're not at war right now, are we?
Who can guarantee
that tomorrow
a war won't break out?
Dad, can you stop trying to scare me?
I am not just being alarmist.
Do you understand?
Dad,
have you noticed?
Whenever the military is mentioned,
you immediately get so formal.
Like you're about to charge into battle.
If we came just to see these gadgets,
and put together a team for it,
then this trip would be quite worthless.
But just now,
your superior told me
that this is where the unit's
new-type combat forces take off.
So,
I feel the significance is different now.
Just now,
the two civilian technical experts
have made their appraisal.
You can use them with confidence.
There are no backdoors.
As for data collection,
the initiative, and even the power of life and death,
are entirely in the hands of the users.
Professor Xu is right.
Every manufacturer providing us with products
is a unit that has
national defense production qualifications.
In short,
we're all on the same side.
Therefore,
you can use them with confidence.
Actually,
simulation training at this technical level
can only address the most basic combined arms modes.
In short,
it's what Battalion Commander Guo just introduced:
the preliminary concept of the Value Cube.
But to form an organic whole,
we must bring out the equipment's
and personnel's true inherent value.
However, the manifestation of this value
depends on massive amounts of data and information.
Professor Xu and I just discussed it,
and we'll integrate our ready-made
research results for simulation training
into your platform,
thereby comprehensively improving
the new-type combat forces'
and traditional equipment's
combined efficiency.
Right.
It's completely free. We won't charge a penny.
That's wonderful.
Thank you, experts, for answering our questions,
and sharing valuable experience.
Although this issue is resolved,
the lessons it leaves behind
are still worth our reflection.
Exactly. Exactly.
Let's imagine.
If we were to take this matter
and reverse the current procedure,
going through it all over again,
would the outcome
be any better?
Through that lesson just now,
I am
deeply moved,
and filled with emotion.
I've learned a great deal.
Deputy Brigade Commander Suo,
I was young and arrogant,
lacking in self-control.
I was ignorant,
and poorly disciplined.
The other day, I said a bunch of
uncultured and impolite things
that caused you great emotional harm.
I'm sorry.
Miss,
please don't do this.
You're making me embarrassed.
Please, don't.
If you don't forgive me,
I'd be too ashamed to get up.
No, no.
I forgive you. I forgive you.
I hope you can forgive me too.
No, no.
Let's shake hands.
We're all good friends.
Sir!
Sir,
I'm young,
and inexperienced.
But I'm very willing
to serve the military's national defense development.
I hope you can give me another chance
to continue our cooperation.
You little girl,
what other chance do you need?
There's a pile of contracts waiting for you to sign.
Does that mean you agree?
Don't try to trap me.
I don't have that much power.
Before the experts arrived,
we had already reported to our superiors.
As long as the experts prove it feasible,
and sign off on it,
and most importantly,
the trial training is successful,
the contract can be signed immediately.
Our Sir is just too adorable.
Much cuter than the rigid and dogmatic Guo Zijian.
Report!
Well, Sir,
I understand
that the Wind Rider Battalion is a key project,
but our Hurricane Battalion...
All right.
I knew you'd speak up.
Don't worry.
You won't be short on budget.
Thank you, Sir.
All right, all right. Let's start the meeting.
Good stuff.
This simulation training system
is really good stuff.
After using it just now,
I really got the feeling
of having a million troops under my command.
It's your treat this time, right?
My treat.
Tell me,
what do you want to eat?
I heard that
before we left,
Sister-in-law packed you some homemade pickles.
Enough!
Out of the question.
Let me tell you,
don't even think about those pickles.
My wife left them for me.
No, no.
Why are you so stingy?
You're almost as bad as Liu Wangyuan.
As bad?
How did you know
I had some pickles?
Guo Zijian,
are you spying on me?
Tell me,
who was it?
Who told you?
It's a secret.
A secret, huh?
What?
If we don't spar a bit,
you won't tell the truth, right?
Can you even beat me?
Even if I can't, I have to try.
Besides, who says I can't beat you?
Battalion Commander Jiang.
Staff Officer Liang.
Carry on. Carry on.
Good stuff.
Really good stuff.
Share some pickles with me.
Out of the question.
What's wrong?
Things are wrapped up now.
When are you taking Chen Xiaoshan mountain climbing?
What mountain climbing?
Did you forget?
You promised her.
Did I promise?
I forgot.
She's already left, so it doesn't matter.
If you act like this,
girls will get angry.
You know about this stuff?
Why wouldn't I?
I had a senior classmate before.
His girlfriend
broke up with him for this exact reason.
Was it really a senior classmate?
Yeah.
You don't need to worry about this.
Chen Xiaoshan and I aren't like that.
So,
it's not an issue.
Report.
Come in.
Deputy Brigade Commander Suo.
"Wind Rider Battalion's Sim Training Practice
on the Scientific Operation of the Value Cube"
has been forwarded by the Theater Army.
Please take a look.
Liang Hong probably sent it to Deputy Army Commander Liang,
who then recommended it.
That's not what happened.
You know about it?
The Brigade Commander recommended it.
The Brigade Commander?
I see.
The Brigade Commander used to be a Director of Operations.
So he's naturally well-connected
within the military hierarchy.
Don't talk nonsense without any evidence.
As the Chief of Operations and Training Section,
you should focus on your own work.
Understood.
But...
since this has caused such a stir,
won't the Group Army
take some action after this?
So you sensed it too.
It seems the big battle to test the results
is about to begin.
Hurry up and get ready.
Yes, sir.
Dismissed.
Staff Officer Liang.
How about we do this after dinner?
There's a unit dinner later.
Finish today's work today.
There will be other things to do after dinner.
Staff Officer Liang,
where do you get
so much energy and stamina every day?
Dad.
Dad, calm down first.
I understand.
I'll go ask for leave right away.
I'll rush back tonight.
Okay, bye.
Staff Officer Liang, what's wrong?
My mom had a sudden heart attack and is in the ER.
Wait, Staff Officer Liang.
Don't worry.
Well... um...
Fall in! Fall in!
Hurry! Fall in!
Wait.
Staff Officer Liang...
Comrades.
We just got an enemy intel report from theater joint command.
The enemy,
with a force of two battalions,
equipped with drones and air assault gear,
will, in twelve hours,
target our
defensive zone's
key chokepoint,
Dongjia Town,
with a surprise attack.
To ensure the safety of the Group Army's rear,
and to prevent the enemy
from using it as a breakthrough point
to divide and encircle our forces,
I order the Wind Rider Battalion
to prepare all troops and weapons
and rapidly deploy toward Dongjia Town.
You must, before the enemy arrives,
seize
the Dongjia Town government building.
This not only means that your
unit dinner tonight is canceled,
but it also
requires you to maintain high morale
and sharp tactics
to face this battle.
Are you confident?
We are! We are! We are!
Report!
Speak.
Sir.
May I ask who our opponent is?
No comment.
Go prepare.
Yes, sir!
Battalion, attention!
Except for battalion staff and company commanders,
all other personnel, return immediately.
Per combat readiness level requirements,
complete preparations for supplies,
equipment,
and personal gear.
Mess squad,
prepare dry rations immediately,
and distribute them during the movement.
Yes, sir!
Everyone, right face!
Liang Hong.
Liang Hong!
Double time, march!
Here!
Immediately confirm
the geographical location of Dongjia Town,
and use the BeiDou System for precise positioning.
At the same time,
you must complete
dynamic reconnaissance of the movement route,
and consider
the requirements for night movement.
All new-type combat forces must immediately initiate
combat readiness level transition.
Yes, sir!
1st Company!
Here!
1st Company is ordered,
along with attached recon, EW, fire, and air defense
forces,
to initiate a level-one combat response immediately.
In twenty minutes,
as the advance unit,
depart.
And make sure
to stay in contact with our battalion command
at all times.
Yes, sir!
Yang Maolin!
Here!
You are ordered to lead the Special Ops Platoon independently.
Depart immediately.
Choose your own route and method.
Once you reach the outskirts of Dongjia Town,
report to me immediately.
Yes, sir!
Special Ops Platoon, right face!
Double time, march!
2nd Company, 3rd Company,
and all other auxiliary branches,
standby for orders.
Await my deployment at any time.
Yes, sir!
Comrades,
although recent training has been good,
I found that some comrades among you
seem reluctant to obey my orders.
This is unacceptable.
I hold a master's degree in military command.
I have participated in Group Army, Theater Army,
and Theater Command exercises, over thirty in total.
I was commended by the Theater Command as an outstanding staff officer.
Company Commander,
it is time to depart.
You can talk on the way.
In short,
obey orders and follow commands.
I will never allow anyone to act on their own.
Report!
Staff Officer Zeng Muhan from battalion command is here.
What is he doing here?
Hello, Company Commander Wang.
I am Battalion Staff Officer Zeng Muhan.
The Battalion Commander assigned us to act with 1st Company.
Are you attached to me, or am I attached to you?
1st Company is the main assault company,
so naturally,
we are attached to you.
As long as the subordination is clear,
things will be easy.
I thought the Battalion Commander sent an Imperial inspector.
You must be joking, Company Commander Wang.
It is getting late.
Let's hurry up and move out.
Is everyone ready?
We are ready!
Move out!
Everyone, right face!
Double time, march!
Hu Zhenhua.
Yes, sir.
What exactly is your staff section doing?
The intel is just a bunch of webpages.
Why hasn't it been compiled?
Sorry.
It was my oversight.
I'll compile it right now.
Staff Officer Liang.
Yes, sir.
You're not the only one in the staff section.
If you can't handle it all,
you should delegate the tasks.
Don't hold things up.
Understood.
It's my fault.
What's wrong with you today?
Nothing.
Alright, the information has been sent over.
Dongjia Town.
It used to be a mining area.
Mostly populated by transients.
The coal here was mined out a few years ago.
So most of the people have left.
It's said that the current town government
only left two guards behind.
This mining area has a distinct feature.
The underground network is very complex.
Engaging in combat in a place like this,
there's no room to maneuver.
This will be a tough battle.
There's no way to gather the opponent's intel for now.
Then we'll gather it as we fight.
Yes, sir.
Sir.
The Group Army combat command center just called.
All the sites of the remote observation system
have been connected.
The Theater Army and Group Army headquarters,
as well as relevant experts from two academies,
and Professor Zhang,
are already at their respective observation systems
seated and ready to observe.
Good.
Technology really is a great thing.
Notify Ma Mingguo
and ask him to cooperate.
To cover every angle throughout the process
and closely monitor all participating units.
This time we need to carefully dissect
this little sparrow, the Wind Rider Battalion.
Yes, sir. I'll notify him immediately.
Good.
First Company.
Reporting. First Company, Wang Qilin.
We received a notice from Exercise Control.
A portion of the enemy's forces
is already making a motorized movement toward Dongjia Town.
First Company is ordered to speed up your movement.
Yes, sir.
Order the whole company to speed up.
Our current speed is already fast enough.
I can't believe Guo Zijian still dares to accelerate.
This kid
has guts.
Professor Zhang.
Calling us here tonight...
Is there some special significance to this exercise?
What significance?
We won't have the answer until the exercise ends.
Putting on such a big show. Who are we fighting?
All I know is we're ordered to seize Dongjia Town.
Other than that, I know absolutely nothing.
A blind fight, huh.
But with your methods, Long Yuanshan,
there's no way you don't have a clue.
An offensive and defensive battle
in a nearly abandoned small town
doesn't allow for a campaign-level decisive battle.
Plus,
we're only allowed to deploy a total force of two battalions.
So I'm guessing
the opponent is a Combined Arms Battalion.
The only Combined Arms Battalions that can spar with you now
are those two "Winds".
Reporting!
Brigade Commander Long,
you actually guessed right.
It's Guo Zijian's Wind Rider Battalion.
There aren't many you'd call a worthy opponent.
I've heard a lot about this Guo Zijian.
This time, I'm going to properly face
this legendary figure.
Let's see if he's a true hero
or just a phony.
Since the Wind Rider Battalion was founded,
this is their first battle against our Black Mamba.
I hope they don't disappoint me.
Light Infantry Company 1 has finished boarding!
Awaiting orders!
Move out!
Attention, all platoons.
At the intersection ahead,
get off the highway
and switch to the national road.
Company Commander,
why are we switching to the national road?
Look.
Based on the map,
switching to the national road saves us
over 20 kilometers of travel.
This is the only way to arrive on time.
Look at this speed.
That is quite fast.
Commander Ma.
Sir is here.
Sir.
It is so late.
What instructions do you have for me at this hour?
Have a seat.
This exercise is an unexpected situation.
You fall directly under the Theater Army.
I have no authority to command you.
But for your unconditional cooperation,
I express my gratitude.
Sir.
I do not deserve such praise.
I am not finished yet.
Wind Rider Battalion
is making its first appearance before Theater leadership.
That is why I specifically deployed you.
Understood?
Understood. Please rest assured, Sir.
Currently, all channels remain clear.
We will absolutely not miss a single detail.
With you here, of course I am assured.
Where are we now?
Staff Officer Zeng,
why did we switch to the national road?
Company Commander Wang! Company Commander Wang!
This is Zeng Muhan. This is Zeng Muhan.
First Company, Wang Qilin. Go ahead.
Company Commander Wang,
the national highway hasn't been scouted in advance.
The road conditions are unknown.
And it only has two lanes.
The convoy formation is too dense.
If we encounter an ambush...
...or an air raid,
the vehicles will struggle to disperse.
We will suffer heavy losses.
Our main priority right now is movement speed.
Speed is crucial.
If we encounter long-range artillery fire...
...or an air assault,
how do we handle it?
The enemy situation report is already very clear.
They are moving toward Dongjia Town at full speed.
An ambush halfway is impossible.
I suggest
the convoy immediately open up a safe distance.
The air defense unit should disperse,
turn on the anti-aircraft radar,
and step up air defense alerts.
Staff Officer Zeng.
I know
you performed excellently in the recent competition.
But you've also heard of
the armchair strategist, right?
Company Commander Wang,
it's exactly out of consideration for actual combat
that I'm making this suggestion to you.
The validity of the enemy situation report
is only guaranteed before it's issued.
Once it's issued,
anything can happen.
It might even be a trap.
Staff Officer Zeng,
are you teaching me how to be a Company Commander?
I wouldn't dare.
Enough, Staff Officer Zeng.
The battle is imminent.
I won't allow anyone
to question my commanding abilities.
Your current task
is to manage the battalion's recon unit well.
Understood.
In that case,
our unit and the First Company's convoy
will maintain a proper distance.
Distance approved.
But falling behind and delaying the battle
won't just mean missing out on the action.
Slow down.
Maintain a safe distance.
Yes, sir.
Report!
Radar has detected two...
No...
three helicopters approaching along the highway.
How far are they?
They were intentionally evading radar
and suddenly popped up.
They are...
less than two kilometers away.
That fast?
Notify all vehicles.
Turn off lights and engines.
Coast forward.
Prepare for a surprise attack.
Yes, sir.
Company Commander Wang! Company Commander Wang!
Three enemy gunships are approaching you.
Less than three kilometers away.
Disperse the convoy immediately
and set up anti-air defenses.
Deputy Company Commander Xu, order the troops.
Enemy gunships will be overhead shortly.
Take cover and prepare anti-air defenses.
Yes, sir.
Driver, lights off, pull over.
Attention, all platoons.
Opposing Force gunships will be overhead shortly.
All vehicles, slow down and turn off lights immediately.
Anti-air units attached to the First Company,
prepare for anti-air defense immediately!
Reporting, Company Commander!
Half the company is declared KIA.
They are out of the fight.
Deputy Company Commander Xu,
you take command.
They're totally off the playbook.
Company Commander,
how can you do this at a time like this?
The pre-battle report
stated the enemy had no armed helicopters.
They're breaking the rules. I want a Reprimand.
A Reprimand can wait until after the battle.
We're still in the middle of a fight right now.
Zhiqiang, I've already made my decision.
For the rest of the battle,
you take command.
Since setting out, Wang Qilin
has only issued two orders,
and half his forces are already wiped out.
What is he good for?
Where's their anti-air defense?
What has Zeng Muhan been doing?
Zeng Muhan...
He just reported in.
First Company's convoy has diverted to the highway.
Their formation is a bit too tight.
Why didn't you warn First Company?
I...
What were you doing?
I'm sorry.
I just zoned out.
Zoned out?
Staff Officer Liang.
Because you zoned out,
I lost most of a reinforced company.
I'm sorry. It's my responsibility.
I will bear the consequences.
Can you afford to?
I can accept a misjudgment made after careful thought,
but I will absolutely not tolerate
a slack work attitude.
You're my chief staff officer.
You zoned out.
How am I supposed to fight this battle?
Guo Zijian!
Could you be a little more polite?
Polite?
Polite to whom?
Will the enemy be polite to you?
This is a battlefield!
So many men were wiped out before reaching the battlefield!
Who can they go cry to?
Everything you say makes sense,
but you shouldn't be unforgiving when right.
That's how I am. So what?
I'm telling you all,
we are fighting a war right now.
Pull yourselves together!
Yes, sir!
Company Commander Wang.
We can't stay here.
We must keep moving forward.
Staff Officer Zeng...
I've had
this old issue with low blood sugar.
It's acting up again.
The 1st Company...
I'm leaving it to you for now.
Staff Officer Zeng,
you're the staff officer from the battalion.
Please take command of the troops.
Right now,
the 1st Company is counting on you.
Where's the Political Instructor?
He's already been eliminated.
He's sulking up ahead.
All right.
I'll cover for you until you recover.
All personnel of the 1st Company,
this is Zeng Muhan.
From now on,
you are under my command.
All operational vehicles and personnel,
mount up immediately.
Form a single column,
maintain spacing,
and advance rapidly.
Meanwhile,
one recon vehicle
is to push forward and scout the road.
The attached battalion air defense radar
must operate intermittently,
and keep its distance from the main force.
Security detachment, stay alert.
All disabled vehicles and personnel,
pull over to the roadside.
Stay safe.
As for everything else,
wait for further notice
after we move out.
Sir.
According to Exercise Control's statistics,
Long Yuanshan's long-range interception just now
took 60% of the Combined Arms 1st Company out of action.
Barring any surprises,
this company
is just one step away
from completely losing its combat effectiveness.
There is the Horseshoe Effect on the Western battlefield.
Sir,
I think
the 1st Company is demonstrating it right here.
1st Company.
Reporting to the Battalion Commander.
This is Zeng Muhan.
Were all of the 1st Company's commanding officers KIA?
Why are you in command?
The Political Instructor was KIA.
The Company Commander had a sudden medical emergency.
I am currently acting as the 1st Company's commander.
Awaiting your orders, Battalion Commander.
Report the 1st Company's current status.
All personnel and equipment have been regrouped.
We are rapidly maneuvering toward Dongjia Town.
Step up reconnaissance.
Seize favorable terrain as quickly as possible.
The enemy is equipped with air power.
They will secure the favorable terrain before we do.
I am working on a battle plan.
Good.
Report any enemy movements immediately.
Yes, sir.
They still managed to exploit a loophole.
What do you mean?
The use of Air Assault.
Your staff team,
why didn't you make a plan for it earlier?
It's mainly because this Air Assault brigade
is too far away.
I calculated the distance at the time.
Even if
we used helicopters to extract the 1st Company,
the time it'd take compared to going there ourselves
would be exactly the same.
But at least it wouldn't let the enemy
succeed so easily.
It's already in the past.
So let's drop it, okay?
The battle isn't over yet.
Mountain Eagle, Mountain Eagle.
This is Honey Badger.
This is Mountain Eagle.
Go ahead.
I'm approaching the target.
Concealment complete.
Awaiting orders.
Find the enemy leaders and execute a decapitation strike.
This is currently
the only way to turn the tide.
Honey Badger copies.
If only we had a few more Yang Maolins.
We're still short on manpower.
Battalion Commander Guo.
If you think I'm incompetent,
you can submit a report.
I can leave at any time.
I wasn't aiming that at you.
You're overthinking it.
What's going on with you two today?
One is prickly all over,
poking everyone in sight.
And the other just lets himself get poked.
If you two keep this attitude today,
how are we supposed to fight this battle?
Reporting, Company Commander.
Our company has reached the outskirts of Dongjia Town.
Since the enemy chose air maneuver,
they couldn't have brought heavy equipment.
It's highly likely one or two light infantry companies.
In that case,
even though we lack heavy equipment,
we have the upper hand with other gear.
We can put up a fight.
It was just a thought.
I haven't thought it through yet.
As a commander,
you must think things through
one or two steps ahead,
even three or four steps.
I've decided
to gather all the equipment
and forces of First Company.
First, we'll secure the key point in Dongjia Town
and hold it until backup arrives.
Once the reinforcements get here,
we'll launch a full-scale assault on the town hall.
But...
Enough.
It's settled.
Wait a minute.
I don't think that'll work.
It's clearly an opportunity. Why not?
First Company has taken heavy casualties.
Even if they don't have heavy weapons,
we aren't fit for a high-intensity assault.
Unless the target is clear
and an important stronghold,
otherwise,
our heavy weapons won't give us much of an edge.
Then you tell me,
how should we fight?
I suggest
dividing our men and gear into two groups.
One group
will advance to the jungle south of the town hall
and stay hidden on standby.
The other group
will infiltrate light to seek combat opportunities.
Meanwhile, conduct a full recon of Dongjia Town
to locate the enemy's
key defense positions
and provide exact coordinates for our heavy firepower.
Fine.
Let's do that.
I'll implement it immediately.
Before and after initiating the operation,
report promptly to the Battalion Commander.
Yes, sir.
Sir.
Battalion Commander.
First Company reached the outskirts of Dongjia Town.
Here is their proposed combat plan.
Approved.
Add one more thing.
Dongjia Town is an old mining area.
They must watch out for tunnels during urban combat.
Yes, sir.
The Opposing Force's tactical skills are solid.
The defense points they built are quite tricky.
Echeloned from front to back,
staggered and arranged together,
supporting each other.
Interesting.
Why does it look familiar?
Look, guys.
Doesn't this look like
the assignment our Platoon Leader gave me last time?
The 404th Brigade's modern urban combat tactics.
It really does.
It's just a pity
Platoon Leader Yang isn't with us today.
And Staff Officer Zeng is too busy for us.
How about
we send our preliminary assessments
to the Battalion Commander first?
Sounds good to me.
There are six target points in total.
These kids really did us proud.
They actually figured out it's the 404th Brigade.
Since the exercise began,
this is the best news I've heard.
Hu Zhenhua.
Here, sir!
Order the Long-Range Artillery unit to launch
precision strikes on the above targets.
Yes, sir.
Why isn't the Long-Range Artillery assessment out yet?
Battalion Commander!
This is way too coincidental.
We were just about to activate the Long-Range Artillery,
and it got wiped out.
Staff Officer Zeng.
Battalion Command just reported.
The 2nd and 3rd Companies
will take another 20 minutes
to reach the outskirts of Dongjia Town.
They will then mass forces for a full-scale assault.
Then why don't we strike first?
We could even claim top credit.
Personal credit is secondary.
Coordinating the whole battle is what matters most.
Then according to you,
how do we fight?
Before the Opposing Force's heavy firepower arrives,
we infiltrate their defense zone
to neutralize their heavy weapon advantage.
I don't think so.
In the current situation,
military textbooks are very clear.
We'll soon face an urban meat grinder.
All urban combat
is a knife fight in a phone booth.
We can't rely on large-scale heavy weapons to crush them.
Instead,
the piecemeal annihilation tactic of small assault groups
is the key to victory.
I support Staff Officer Zeng's idea.
A few days ago,
when we studied urban combat,
Staff Officer Liang also mentioned it.
A commander's influence on the course of battle
is much smaller than in the field.
Many things depend on the commander
and the initiative of individual soldiers.
I know,
but this is Dongjia Town.
It's not Moscow or Berlin,
let alone Mogadishu or Grozny.
But they all share
the basic features of modern urban combat.
On the way here,
I gained a comprehensive understanding
of Dongjia Town's terrain.
Because of the mining area's drainage,
there are many underground tunnels.
If we can make good use
of these underground tunnels
to infiltrate secretly,
it will solve a lot of problems.
Fine.
Into the tunnels.
Deputy Company Commander Xu.
Here.
Order the troops.
After entering the tunnels,
form three-man teams and advance alternately.
Be careful not to alert the enemy.
Yes, sir.
Platoon Commander.
I guess the Opposing Force's commander, like ours,
must be commanding from a command vehicle.
They won't set up a physical command post.
You don't need to lecture me on that.
Even if we're looking for the command vehicle,
we have to find clues from the guard deployment
of their security forces.
Any discoveries?
No.
Although the town hall is the combat focus,
it's obvious
the command center isn't there.
Battalion Commander.
The 2nd Company and attached units
have all reached the east side of Dongjia Town
and are ready for the assault.
The 3rd Company and attached units
have all reached the west side of Dongjia Town
and are ready for the assault.
Orders:
assault the town hall in five minutes.
Report.
Opposing Force heavy equipment is under ten kilometers away.
In 15 minutes,
they will form a pincer attack.
The 2nd and 3rd Companies
will push deep into Dongjia Town
and immediately form an interlocking position.
Seize three to four high points
to counter their reinforcements.
Understood.
Second Company, Third Company,
immediately organize by platoons
to form small assault teams.
According to the established battle plan,
upon engaging the enemy,
immediately advance deep into the town.